Tisch Library Records UA137
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Buildings and Plans, 1940 -- 2009; 1960 -- 1990; UA137.005; 3.65 Linear Feet; 90 Digital Object(s) Of the 90 digital objects, one digital object comprises 59 files.; 91 Megabytes
  - Wessell Library, shelving, 1963 -- 1965; UA137.005.018.00010 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, staff planning, 1965; UA137.005.018.00011 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library, sprinklers, 1988; UA137.005.018.00012 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Wessell Library move, 1965; UA137.005.018.00013 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - RFP Document for an automated library system, 1901 -- 1985; UA137.005.018.00014 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Support materials [1 of 2], 1985; UA137.005.018.00015 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Support materials [2 of 2], 1985; UA137.005.018.00016 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Tisch Family Library - Artist rendering, 1990 -- 1995; UA137.005.019.00001 (Box Shared 3)
- Correspondence, 1853 -- 1989; 1960 -- 1980; UA137.006; 1.05 Linear Feet
  This series contains general correspondence files not associated with any individual librarian, the correspondence files of Joseph Komidar, and the correspondence files of Murray Martin.
  These materials are arranged into three alphabetical runs. The first alphabetical run is made up of the general correspondence files. The second is made up of Komidar's correspondence files. The third is made up of Martin's correspondence files.
  - Library correspondence [General], 1853 -- 1861; UA137.006.018.00017 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Library correspondence [General], 1862 -- 1905; UA137.006.018.00018 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Library correspondence [General], 1906 -- 1930; UA137.006.018.00019 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Library correspondence [General], 1931 -- 1950; UA137.006.018.00020 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence A-E [Komidar], 1940 -- 1975; UA137.006.018.00021; Komindar, Joseph (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Library correspondence [General], 1953 -- 1983; UA137.006.018.00022 (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence F-G [Komidar], 1951 -- 1971; UA137.006.018.00023; Komindar, Joseph (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence H-J [Komidar], 1940 -- 1975; UA137.006.018.00024; Komindar, Joseph (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence K-L [Komidar], 1952 -- 1976; UA137.006.018.00025; Komindar, Joseph (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence M-P [Komidar], 1944 -- 1973; UA137.006.020.00001; Komindar, Joseph (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence R-S [Komidar], 1954 -- 1975; UA137.006.020.00002; Komindar, Joseph (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence T-Z [Komidar], 1949 -- 1974; UA137.006.020.00003; Komindar, Joseph (Box UA137 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence [Komidar], 1970 -- 1981; UA137.006.020.00004; Komindar, Joseph (Box 20)
  - Norbert Wiener Forum [Komidar], 1982 -- 1987; UA137.006.020.00005; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence A [Martin], 1982 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00006; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence B [Martin], 1981 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00007; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence C [Martin], 1982 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00008; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence D [Martin], 1981 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00009; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence E [Martin], 1981 -- 1987; UA137.006.020.00010; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence F [Martin], 1981 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00011; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence G [Martin], 1982 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00012; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence H [Martin], 1983 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00013; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence J [Martin], 1983 -- 1987; UA137.006.020.00014; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence K [Martin], 1982 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00015; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence L [Martin], 1981 -- 1989; UA137.006.020.00016; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence Mc [Martin], 1982 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00017; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence M [Martin], 1982 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00018; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence N [Martin], 1983 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00019; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence O [Martin], 1985 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00020; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence P [Martin], 1982 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00021; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence Q-R [Martin], 1983 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00022; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence S [Martin], 1983 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00023; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence T [Martin], 1983 -- 1987; UA137.006.020.00024; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence U-V [Martin], 1984 -- 1987; UA137.006.020.00025; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence W-Y [Martin], 1986 -- 1988; UA137.006.020.00026; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
  - Correspondence Wessell Staff [Martin], 1988; UA137.006.020.00027; Martin, Murray (Box 20)
- Subject Files, 1861 -- 2019; 1950 -- 1990; UA137.007; 13.7 Linear Feet
  This series contains subject files, including general subject files not associated with any individual librarian; University Librarian Joseph Komidar's subject files; University Librarian Murray Martin's subject files; Reference Librarian Margaret Gooch's subject files; University Librarian Wayne Powell's Subject Files; and Librarian Connie Reik's subject files; and Digital Library license agreements.
  This series is arranged into seven sub-series. The first three are arranged alphabetically by subject; these are general subject files, Komidar subject files, and Martin subject files. The Gooch subject files, Powell subject files, and Reik subject files are arranged in original order. The Digital Library deposit licenses are arranged chronologically.
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  - General subject files, 1861 -- 1997; UA137.007.001
    - Aaron Cohen Associates, 1982; UA137.007.021.00001 (Box 21)
    - Account book, 1930 -- 1948; UA137.007.021.00002 (Box 21)
    - Acquisitions, 1956 -- 1971; UA137.007.021.00003 (Box 21)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1969 -- 1972; UA137.007.021.00004 (Box 21)
    - ALA Library Survey, 1925; UA137.007.021.00005 (Box 21)
    - Alumni correspondence, 1965 -- 1966; UA137.007.021.00006 (Box 21)
    - Archives, 1960 -- 1970; UA137.007.021.00007 (Box 21)
    - Archives, 1990 -- 1994; UA137.007.021.00008 (Box 21)
    - Arts and Sciences Library statistics, Volume 1, 1955 -- 1975; UA137.007.021.00009 (Box 21)
    - Arts and Sciences Library statistics, Volume 2, 1956 -- 1981; UA137.007.021.00010 (Box 21)
    - Arts and Sciences Library statistics, Volume 3, 1956 -- 1978; UA137.007.021.00011 (Box 21)
    - Arts and Sciences Library statistics, Volume 5, 1974 -- 1978; UA137.007.021.00012 (Box 21)
    - Audio-Visual, 1967 -- 1986; UA137.007.021.00013 (Box 21)
    - Automated library system, 1984 -- 1987; UA137.007.021.00014 (Box 21)
    - Beal Technique survey, 1974 -- 1975; UA137.007.021.00015 (Box 21)
    - Bibliographic Instruction, 1929 -- 1951; UA137.007.021.00016 (Box 21)
    - Book processing, 1967 -- 1979; UA137.007.021.00017 (Box 21)
    - Budget, 1928 -- 1965; UA137.007.021.00018 (Box 21)
    - Budget, 1966 -- 1979; UA137.007.021.00019 (Box 21)
    - Budget, 1980 -- 1982; UA137.007.021.00020 (Box 21)
    - Budget, 1983 -- 1985; UA137.007.021.00021 (Box 21)
    - Budget, 1986 -- 1988; UA137.007.022.00001 (Box 22)
    - Budget endowment funds, 1920 -- 1951; UA137.007.022.00002 (Box 22)
    - Carnegie Institution Publications, 1940 -- 1942; UA137.007.022.00003 (Box 22)
    - Cataloging procedures, 1956 -- 1963; UA137.007.022.00004 (Box 22)
    - Cataloging procedures, 1978 -- 1986; UA137.007.022.00005 (Box 22)
    - Chapel talks (Walkley?), 1930 -- 1937; UA137.007.022.00006 (Box 22)
    - Child Study Library, 1964 -- 1969; UA137.007.022.00007 (Box 22)
    - Circulation, 1932 -- 1956; UA137.007.022.00008 (Box 22)
    - Circulation, 1957 -- 1967; UA137.007.022.00009 (Box 22)
    - Circulation, 1978 -- 1980; UA137.007.022.00010 (Box 22)
    - Collection Management Program, 1989; UA137.007.022.00011 (Box 22)
    - Cooperation, 1959 -- 1971; UA137.007.022.00012 (Box 22)
    - Cooperation, Boston area, 1959 -- 1968; UA137.007.022.00013 (Box 22)
    - Crane Library, 1935 -- 1968; UA137.007.022.00014 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Lab, 1975 -- 1976; UA137.007.022.00015 (Box 22)
    - Delphi Questionnaire, 1974; UA137.007.022.00016 (Box 22)
    - End of semester projections, 1979 -- 1983; UA137.007.022.00017 (Box 22)
    - Engineering Library, 1940 -- 1954; UA137.007.022.00018 (Box 22)
    - Exhibits, 1966 -- 1974; UA137.007.022.00019 (Box 22)
    - Exhibits, 1983 -- 1990; UA137.007.022.00020 (Box 22)
    - Expenditures analysis, 1973 -- 1974; UA137.007.022.00021 (Box 22)
    - Fine Arts, 1976; UA137.007.022.00022 (Box 22)
    - Flood, 1980; UA137.007.022.00023 (Box 22)
    - Friends of the Library, 1955 -- 1959; UA137.007.022.00024 (Box 22)
    - Gifts, 1910 -- 1956; UA137.007.022.00025 (Box 22)
    - Gifts, 1957 -- 1974; UA137.007.022.00026 (Box 22)
    - Gifts, monetary, 1958 -- 1964; UA137.007.022.00027 (Box 22)
    - Gifts, monetary, 1965 -- 1978; UA137.007.022.00028 (Box 22)
    - Ginn Library Annual Reports, 1930 -- 1951; UA137.007.022.00029 (Box 22)
    - Gloss, George, 1964; UA137.007.022.00030 (Box 22)
    - Gott Memorial English Room, 1950 -- 1972; UA137.007.022.00031 (Box 22)
    - Jackson, W. Carl, 1981; UA137.007.022.00032 (Box 22)
    - Keough, Floence, 1972; UA137.007.022.00033 (Box 22)
    - Komidar retirement reception, 1981; UA137.007.022.00034 (Box 22)
    - Kresge Foundation grant, 1986 -- 1987; UA137.007.022.00035 (Box 22)
    - Kresge Foundation grant, 1988 -- 1989; UA137.007.022.00036 (Box 22)
    - Librarians Handbook, 1989 -- 1992; UA137.007.022.00037 (Box 22)
    - Library directory, 1968 -- 1971; UA137.007.022.00038 (Box 22)
    - Library history, 1861 -- 1966; UA137.007.022.00039 (Box 22)
    - Library hours, 1959 -- 1980; UA137.007.023.00001 (Box 23)
    - Library information for students and faculty, 1957 -- 1970; UA137.007.023.00002 (Box 23)
    - Library leaflets, 1963 -- 1994; UA137.007.023.00003 (Box 23)
    - Library statistics reported, 1932 -- 1970; UA137.007.023.00004 (Box 23)
    - Library guides, 1975 -- 1981; UA137.007.023.00005 (Box 23)
    - Martin reports, 1982; UA137.007.023.00006 (Box 23)
    - McDonald, David - Memoranda, 1990; UA137.007.023.00007 (Box 23)
    - McDonald, David - Memoranda, 1991; UA137.007.023.00008 (Box 23)
    - McDonald, David - Memoranda, 1992 -- 1997; UA137.007.023.00009 (Box 23)
    - Manuals and procedures, 1975 -- 1982; UA137.007.023.00010 (Box 23)
    - Medical library, 1945 -- 1947; UA137.007.023.00011 (Box 23)
    - National Health Information Center, 1982; UA137.007.023.00012 (Box 23)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1979 -- 1980; UA137.007.023.00013 (Box 23)
    - National Youth Administration, 1935 -- 1942; UA137.007.023.00014 (Box 23)
    - New England Document Conservation Center, 1972 -- 1974; UA137.007.023.00015 (Box 23)
    - New England Deposit Library, 1941 -- 1957; UA137.007.023.00016 (Box 23)
    - Periodicals received, 1949 -- 1988; UA137.007.023.00017 (Box 23)
    - Policies, 1942 -- 1993; UA137.007.023.00018 (Box 23)
    - Position Descriptions, 1959 -- 1990; UA137.007.023.00019 (Box 23)
    - Reports and studies, 1953 -- 1975; UA137.007.023.00020 (Box 23)
    - Retreat, 1984; UA137.007.024.00001 (Box 24)
    - Rules, 1931 -- 1951; UA137.007.024.00002 (Box 24)
    - Sample inventories, 1971 -- 1983; UA137.007.024.00003 (Box 24)
    - Serials holdings, 1969; UA137.007.024.00004 (Box 24)
    - Serials holdings, 1970; UA137.007.024.00005 (Box 24)
    - Serials holdings, 1971; UA137.007.024.00006 (Box 24)
    - Serials holdings, 1972; UA137.007.024.00007 (Box 24)
    - Serials holdings, 1974; UA137.007.024.00008 (Box 24)
    - Serials inventory, 1957; UA137.007.024.00009 (Box 24)
    - Siegenthaler, Myra, correspondence, 1977 -- 1978; UA137.007.024.00010 (Box 24)
      Head of Circulation
    - Siegenthaler, Myra, correspondence, 1979 -- 1982; UA137.007.024.00011 (Box 24)
    - Siegenthaler, Myra, correspondence, 1982 -- 1984; UA137.007.024.00012 (Box 24)
    - Siegenthaler papers, 1983 -- 1984; UA137.007.024.00013 (Box 24)
    - Siegenthaler papers, 1985 -- 1988; UA137.007.024.00014 (Box 24)
    - Statistics, 1953 -- 1966; UA137.007.024.00015 (Box 24)
    - Statistics, 1967 -- 1980; UA137.007.024.00016 (Box 24)
    - Statistics, 1981 -- 1982; UA137.007.024.00017 (Box 24)
    - Statistics, 1983 -- 1985; UA137.007.024.00018 (Box 24)
    - Statistics, Ginn Library, 1969 -- 1980; UA137.007.024.00019 (Box 24)
    - Statistics, Health Sciences Library, 1969 -- 1980; UA137.007.024.00020 (Box 24)
    - Status of Librarians, 1976 -- 1984; UA137.007.024.00021 (Box 24)
    - Study abroad programs, 1966 -- 1967; UA137.007.024.00022 (Box 24)
    - Supplies, 1953; UA137.007.025.00001 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Survey of other libraries, 1955; UA137.007.025.00002 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Taylor, Merrily, UA137.007.025.00003 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - TSARS, 1991 -- 1992; UA137.007.025.00004 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Tufts in Italy, 1961 -- 1968; UA137.007.025.00005 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - TULIPS inauguration slides, 1986; UA137.007.025.00006 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Union List of Serials, 1959 -- 1960; UA137.007.025.00007 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - U.S. Office of Education, 1958; UA137.007.025.00008 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, 1973; UA137.007.025.00009 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, 1993 -- 1994; UA137.007.025.00010 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, Arts and Sciences, 1995; UA137.007.025.00011 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, Chemistry Library, 1992; UA137.007.025.00012 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, Overall response, 1992; UA137.007.025.00013 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, Lufkin, 1992; UA137.007.025.00014 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, Music Library, 1991 -- 1992; UA137.007.025.00015 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, Physics Reading Room, 1992; UA137.007.025.00016 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, survey document, 1991; UA137.007.025.00017 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - User Survey, Wessell Library, 1992; UA137.007.025.00018 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
  - Komidar subject files, 1937 -- 1987; UA137.007.002
    - Acquisitions, 1973 -- 1979; UA137.007.025.00019 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Administration, 1961 -- 1979; UA137.007.025.00020 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Affirmative Action, 1973 -- 1980; UA137.007.025.00021 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Architectural Design Competition, 1963; UA137.007.025.00022 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Archives, 1962 -- 1980; UA137.007.025.00023 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Audio-Visual, 1960 -- 1980; UA137.007.025.00024 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Building survey, 1958 -- 1960; UA137.007.025.00025 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Building survey, 1958 -- 1960; UA137.007.025.00026 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Buildings, 1960 -- 1978; UA137.007.025.00027 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Chemistry, 1961 -- 1980; UA137.007.025.00028 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Child Study Department, 1973 -- 1982; UA137.007.025.00029 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Consortium, 1961; UA137.007.025.00030 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Copyright, 1967 -- 1976; UA137.007.025.00031 (Box UA137 Shared 2)
    - Curriculum Resource Center, 1972 -- 1987; UA137.007.026.00001 (Box 26)
    - Edward R. Murrow Center, 1971 -- 1974; UA137.007.026.00002 (Box 26)
    - Fine Arts, 1965 -- 1980; UA137.007.026.00003 (Box 26)
    - Fletcher, 1957 -- 1980; UA137.007.026.00004 (Box 26)
    - Flood, 1980; UA137.007.026.00005 (Box 26)
    - Freshman Priye, 1937 -- 1966; UA137.007.026.00006 (Box 26)
    - Gifts, 1956 -- 1964; UA137.007.026.00007 (Box 26)
    - Gifts, 1965 -- 1967; UA137.007.026.00008 (Box 26)
    - Gifts, 1968 -- 1970; UA137.007.026.00009 (Box 26)
    - Graduate School, 1957 -- 1965; UA137.007.026.00010 (Box 26)
    - Handicapped, 1977 -- 1979; UA137.007.026.00011 (Box 26)
    - Health Sciences Facilities, 1968 -- 1976; UA137.007.026.00012 (Box 26)
    - Health Sciences Library, 1969 -- 1980; UA137.007.026.00013 (Box 26)
    - Health Sciences Library Budget, 1968 -- 1980; UA137.007.026.00014 (Box 26)
    - Health Sciences Library Services, 1968 -- 1980; UA137.007.026.00015 (Box 26)
    - Library Manpower Conference, 1968; UA137.007.026.00016 (Box 26)
    - Lufkin Library, 1960 -- 1967; UA137.007.026.00017 (Box 26)
    - Medical-Dental Library, 1958 -- 1972; UA137.007.026.00018 (Box 26)
    - Montgomery case, 1966 -- 1967; UA137.007.026.00019 (Box 26)
    - Music, 1974 -- 1981; UA137.007.026.00020 (Box 26)
    - NELINET, 1971 -- 1978; UA137.007.026.00021 (Box 26)
    - Provost, 1957 -- 1980; UA137.007.026.00022 (Box 26)
    - Reference, 1959 -- 1978; UA137.007.026.00023 (Box 26)
    - Reserve Room, 1959 -- 1981; UA137.007.026.00024 (Box 26)
    - Security, 1964 -- 1979; UA137.007.026.00025 (Box 26)
    - Serials, 1956 -- 1974; UA137.007.026.00026 (Box 26)
    - Special Reports, 1957 -- 1976; UA137.007.027.00001 (Box 27)
    - Universalist Historical Society, 1949 -- 1976; UA137.007.027.00002 (Box 27)
  - Martin subject files, 1971 -- 1989; UA137.007.003
    - Allen, Woody, Exhibit, 1988; UA137.007.027.00003 (Box 27)
    - Archives, 1981 -- 1987; UA137.007.027.00004 (Box 27)
    - Arts and Sciences, 1987 -- 1988; UA137.007.027.00005 (Box 27)
    - Arts House, 1982 -- 1987; UA137.007.027.00006 (Box 27)
    - Arts and Sciences Faculty Meetings, 1984 -- 1987; UA137.007.027.00007 (Box 27)
    - Bernstein Center Dedication, 1984; UA137.007.027.00008 (Box 27)
    - Budgets, 1983 -- 1989; UA137.007.027.00009 (Box 27)
    - CEM, 1984; UA137.007.027.00010 (Box 27)
    - CEM, 1902 -- 1985; UA137.007.027.00011 (Box 27)
    - CEM, 1906 -- 1985; UA137.007.027.00012 (Box 27)
    - CEM, General, 1984 -- 1986; UA137.007.027.00013 (Box 27)
    - Circulation, 1981 -- 1982; UA137.007.027.00014 (Box 27)
    - Collection Development, 1988; UA137.007.027.00015 (Box 27)
    - Computer/Communications Resource Committee, 1987; UA137.007.027.00016 (Box 27)
    - Copyright, 1983 -- 1986; UA137.007.027.00017 (Box 27)
    - Council of Deans, 1982 -- 1986; UA137.007.027.00018 (Box 27)
    - Crowe Papers, 1971; UA137.007.027.00019 (Box 27)
    - Culture Today, 1986; UA137.007.027.00020 (Box 27)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1981 -- 1986; UA137.007.027.00021 (Box 27)
    - Davis, Arthur Vining, Foundation, 1988; UA137.007.027.00022 (Box 27)
    - Development, 1982 -- 1984; UA137.007.027.00023 (Box 27)
    - Educational Resources Committee, 1982; UA137.007.027.00024 (Box 27)
    - Engineering, 1981 -- 1988; UA137.007.027.00025 (Box 27)
    - Environmental Research, Education, and Policy Committee, 1984 -- 1987; UA137.007.027.00026 (Box 27)
    - Experimental College, 1988; UA137.007.027.00027 (Box 27)
    - "Eyes on the Prize", 1986 -- 1987; UA137.007.027.00028 (Box 27)
    - Faxon, 1984 -- 1988; UA137.007.028.00001 (Box 28)
    - Federal Assistance Application, 1982; UA137.007.028.00002 (Box 28)
    - Fenway Library Consortium, 1986 -- 1987; UA137.007.028.00003 (Box 28)
    - Fine Arts Library, 1981 -- 1984; UA137.007.028.00004 (Box 28)
    - Fletcher, 1982 -- 1988; UA137.007.028.00005 (Box 28)
    - Friends of the Libraries, 1985 -- 1988; UA137.007.028.00006 (Box 28)
    - Gifts, 1982 -- 1988; UA137.007.028.00007 (Box 28)
    - Ginn Library, 1985 -- 1986; UA137.007.028.00008 (Box 28)
    - Government Publications, 1982 -- 1986; UA137.007.028.00009 (Box 28)
    - Health Sciences Library Committee, 1987 -- 1989; UA137.007.028.00010 (Box 28)
    - Health Sciences Library Committee, 1982 -- 1983; UA137.007.028.00011 (Box 28)
    - Health Sciences Library Committee, 1984; UA137.007.028.00012 (Box 28)
    - Health Sciences Library Committee, 1985 -- 1986; UA137.007.028.00013 (Box 28)
    - Holmes Collection, 1988; UA137.007.028.00014 (Box 28)
    - Human Nutrition Research Center, 1987; UA137.007.028.00015 (Box 28)
    - IAIMS, 1983 -- 1985; UA137.007.028.00016 (Box 28)
    - Information Needs, 1982 -- 1983; UA137.007.028.00017 (Box 28)
    - Institute Planning, 1982; UA137.007.028.00018 (Box 28)
    - Interlibrary Loan, 1985; UA137.007.028.00019 (Box 28)
    - Learning Resources Committe, 1981 -- 1983; UA137.007.028.00020 (Box 28)
    - Lending Services Committee, 1985 -- 1988; UA137.007.028.00021 (Box 28)
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson Committee Reports, 1980 -- 1988; UA137.007.028.00022 (Box 28)
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson Faculty, 1982 -- 1988; UA137.007.028.00023 (Box 28)
    - Library Assistants, 1984; UA137.007.028.00024 (Box 28)
    - Library Committee, 1982 -- 1988; UA137.007.028.00025 (Box 28)
    - Library Cost Study, 1984; UA137.007.028.00026 (Box 28)
    - Library Internship Program, 1987; UA137.007.028.00027 (Box 28)
    - Library Use Survey, 1984; UA137.007.028.00028 (Box 28)
    - Lurie Collection, 1986; UA137.007.028.00029 (Box 28)
    - Massachusetts Board of Library Commissioners, 1988; UA137.007.028.00030 (Box 28)
    - Math/Physics Library, 1982 -- 1986; UA137.007.028.00031 (Box 28)
    - Milliken Fund, 1983; UA137.007.028.00032 (Box 28)
    - Music, 1983 -- 1984; UA137.007.028.00033 (Box 28)
    - Norton, Alice, 1980 -- 1983; UA137.007.028.00034 (Box 28)
    - Norton, Alice, 1984 -- 1986; UA137.007.029.00001 (Box 29)
    - Nutrition, 1982 -- 1986; UA137.007.029.00002 (Box 29)
    - Occupational Therapy, 1982; UA137.007.029.00003 (Box 29)
    - Online Search Services, 1983 -- 1985; UA137.007.029.00004 (Box 29)
    - Planning, 1985 -- 1986; UA137.007.029.00005 (Box 29)
    - Preservation Project, 1980 -- 1987; UA137.007.029.00006 (Box 29)
    - Provost, 1985 -- 1988; UA137.007.029.00007 (Box 29)
    - Public Access Catalog, 1986; UA137.007.029.00008 (Box 29)
    - Re-accreditation Report, 1981; UA137.007.029.00009 (Box 29)
    - Reports, 1984 -- 1987; UA137.007.029.00010 (Box 29)
    - Reserves, 1988; UA137.007.029.00011 (Box 29)
    - Rotberg, Robert, 1987 -- 1989; UA137.007.029.00012 (Box 29)
    - Rousmaniere Management Associates, 1982 -- 1984; UA137.007.029.00013 (Box 29)
    - Sackler Center, 1983 -- 1985; UA137.007.029.00014 (Box 29)
    - Schwab, Henry, Exhibit, 1986; UA137.007.029.00015 (Box 29)
    - Tufts Authors Collection, 1984 -- 1987; UA137.007.029.00016 (Box 29)
    - Tufts Journal, 1982 -- 1987; UA137.007.029.00017 (Box 29)
    - University Library Council, 1981 -- 1988; UA137.007.029.00018 (Box 29)
    - Veterenary School (Grafton Libary), 1982 -- 1987; UA137.007.029.00019 (Box 29)
    - Visiting Committee, 1982 -- 1987; UA137.007.029.00020 (Box 29)
  - Gooch subject files, 1971 -- 2006; UA137.007.004
    - Early Author Talks, 1990 -- 1995; UA137.007.029.00021 (Box 29)
    - [Tisch Library Publications], 1984 -- 2006; UA137.007.029.00022 (Box 29)
    - [Wessell Library Publications], 1980 -- 1991; UA137.007.029.00023 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1990 -- 1991; UA137.007.029.00024 (Box 29)
    - [Electronic Resources Workshops], 1998; UA137.007.029.00025 (Box 29)
    - [Tony Smith Letter], 1992; UA137.007.029.00026 (Box 29)
    - [Program of Events], 1996; UA137.007.029.00027 (Box 29)
    - [Tisch Library Guide], 1996 -- 1997; UA137.007.029.00028 (Box 29)
    - Reference Department: Reference Meetings, 1985 -- 1993; UA137.007.029.00029 (Box 29)
    - Reference Department: Reference Services Librarians Meetings, 1986 -- 1988; UA137.007.029.00030 (Box 29)
    - Reference Department: [Reference Services], 1983 -- 1985; UA137.007.029.00031 (Box 29)
    - Reference Department: Annual Reports, 1971 -- 1980; UA137.007.029.00032 (Box 29)
    - Reference Department: Staff Meetings, 1972 -- 1973; UA137.007.029.00033 (Box 29)
    - Bibliographic Instruction: Bibliographic Instruction Committee, 1975 -- 1983; UA137.007.029.00034 (Box 29)